An Inventory of the United States. Food Administration records XX066
Hoover Institution Archives
- Edwin Paul Shattuck, General Counsel of the United States Grain Corporation (USGC), London office files, 1911-1934, 1957 (Folder 217-234)
  - Foreign obligations, 1919 (Folder 233: 6)
  - C. B. Fox, zone 6, 1919-1920 (Folder 233: 7)
  - General Supply Committee, 1919-1920 (Folder 233: 8)
  - P. H. Ginder, zone 14, 1919 (Folder 233: 9)
  - Carter Glass, 1919 (Folder 233: 10)
  - Globe Grain & Milling Company, 1920 (Folder 233: 11)
  - Gramercy Chocolate Company, 1920 (Folder 233: 12)
  - Gronna Bill to the Committee on Agriculture and Forestry, 1919-1920 (Folder 233: 13)
  - License forms, 1919 (Folder 233: 14)
  - Sales reports, 1920 (Folder 233: 15)
  - European flour relief program, report, 1920 (Folder 233: 16)
  - Stockholders meetings, 1920 (Folder 233: 17)
  - Information memoranda, 1917-1918 (Folder 233: 18-19)
  - H. Hoover, J. Barnes, E. Flesh, cables to and from, 1918-1919 (Folder 233: 20-25)
  - Girard Trust Co. vs. USGC, 1919-1921 (Folder 234: 1-4)
  - Gordon T. Findlay vs. USGC, 1922-1926 (Folder 234: 5-6)
  - Oscar Julius Lundby vs. USGC, 1925-1927 (Folder 234: 7)
  - Disher & Co., vs. USGC, 1918-1927 (Folder 234: 8-10)
  - Lehigh Valley Railroad Co. vs. USGC, 1918-1926 (Folder 234: 11-13)
  - F. Olsen Rasmus vs. USGC, 1918-1920 (Folder 234: 14)
- William Elliot, Federal Food Administrator for South Carolina files, 1917-1919 (Folder 235-238)
  - General file, South Carolina, 1917-1919 (Folder 235: 1-13)
  - General file, South Carolina, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 236: 1-15)
  - General file, South Carolina, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 237: 1-14)
  - General file, South Carolina, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 238: 1-5)
  - General file, Washington, 1917-1919 (Folder 238: 6-15)
- Harry E. Barnard, Federal Food Administrator for Indiana files, 1917-1919 (Folder 239-241)
  - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 239: 1-14)
  - Correspondence, 1917-1919(contd.) (Folder 240: 1-14)
  - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 241: 1-13)
  - Local newspapers with Conservation Proclamation, 1918 (Folder 241: 14-16)
- Organizational (USFA) correspondence file, 1917-1919 (Folder 242)
  - Correspondence, 1917 (Folder 242: 1-16)
  - Correspondence, 1918 (Folder 243: 1-16)
  - Correspondence, 1918 (contd.) (Folder 244: 1-16)
  - Correspondence, 1918-1919 (Folder 245: 1-14)
- Edward M. Flesh, First Vice-President of Food Administration Grain Corporation files, 1914-1928, 1939 (Folder 246-257)
  - A correspondence, 1918-1919 (Folder 246: 1-2)
  - American Consular Service, 1918-1919 (Folder 246: 3)
  - American Embassy, 1919 (Folder 246: 4)
  - Atwood, William G., 1919 (Folder 246: 5)
  - B correspondence, 1919 (Folder 246: 6-7)
  - Baltic states, 1919 (Folder 246: 8)
  - Barber, A. B., 1919 (Folder 246: 9-11)
  - Barley, 1919 (Folder 246: 12)
  - Barnes, Julius H., 1918-1919 (Folder 246)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1919 (Folder 246: 13-19)
    - Correspondence, 1918-1919 (contd.) (Folder 247: 1-11)
    - Diary, 1918-1919 (Folder 247: 12-13)
  - Bodman, Herbert L., 1919. (Folder 247: 14-15)
    See also Lapham, R. D.
  - Bordeaux, 1919 (Folder 247: 16)
  - British business, 1919 (Folder 248: 1)
  - C correspondence, 1919 (Folder 248: 2-3)
  - Cables, 1919 (Folder 248: 4-5)
  - Commission for Relief in Belgium, 1918-1919 (Folder 248: 6-7)
  - Constantinople, 1918-1919 (Folder 248: 8-9)
  - Courier service, 1919 (Folder 248: 10)
  - Crowell, Frank, 1918-1919 (Folder 248: 11)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1919 (Folder 248: 12)
  - D Correspondence, 1918-1919 (Folder 248: 13)
  - Danzig, 1919 (Folder 248: 14-18)
  - Denmark, 1919 (Folder 248: 19-20)
  - Dixon, Gertrude C., 1918-1919 (Folder 249: 1)
  - Durand, E. Dana, 1918-1919 (Folder 249: 2-6)
  - E Correspondence, 1919 (Folder 249: 7)
  - F Correspondence, 1919 (Folder 249: 8)
  - Falmouth, G. C. Fox & Co., 1919 (Folder 249: 9-10)
  - Finland, 1919 (Folder 249: 11-16)
  - Flesh, Edward M., 1919 (Folder 249: 17-18)
  - Flesh, Edward M., 1919 (Folder 250: 1-10)
  - Flour samples, 1919 (Folder 250: 11)
  - Food Administration Grain Corporation, 1918-1919
    - Miscellany correspondence, reports, 1918-1919 (Folder 250: 12-14)
    - Contract with ARA, 1919 (Folder 250: 15-16)
    - Fiscal Report on European Relief Operations of the American Relief Administration; January to August 1919, by Herbert C. Hoover (Folder 251: 1)
  - France, 1918-1919 (Folder 251: 2)
  - G correspondence, 1919 (Folder 251: 3)
  - Galbraith, L. C.
    See Constantinople
  - Gardes, A. H., 1919 (Folder 251: 4)
  - Gay, George I.
    See Commission for Relief in Belgium
  - Glasgow, 1919 (Folder 251: 5)
  - Goode, William A., 1919 (Folder 251: 6)
  - Gorvin, J. H., 1919 (Folder 251: 7)
  - Great Britain, Food Ministry, 1919 (Folder 251: 8)
  - Greece, 1918-1919 (Folder 251: 9)
  - H Correspondence, 1919 (Folder 251: 10-11)
  - Hamburg, 1919 (Folder 251: 12)
  - Hanrahan, D. C.
    See Danzig
  - Le Havre, 1919 (Folder 251: 13)
  - Heins, Howard.
  - Hilton, Edna M., 1918-1919 (Folder 251: 14)
  - Holland, 1918-1919 (Folder 251: 15)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1918-1919 (Folder 252: 1)
  - Hurley, John, 1919 (Folder 252: 2)
  - Hyslop, George K., 1919 (Folder 252: 3-6)
  - I-J correspondence, 1919 (Folder 252: 7)
  - Insurance, 1919 (Folder 252: 8-9)
  - Italy, 1918-1919 (Folder 252: 10)
  - K correspondence, 1919 (Folder 252: 11)
  - L correspondence, 1919 (Folder 252: 12-13)
  - Lands End, 1919 (Folder 252: 14)
  - Lapham, Roger D., 1919. (Folder 252: 15-18)
    See also Bodman, Herbert L.
  - Lapham, Roger D., 1919 (contd.) (Folder 253: 1-3)
  - Liverpool, 1919 (Folder 253: 4)
  - Logan, James, 1919 (Folder 253: 5)
  - M Correspondence, 1919 (Folder 253: 6)
  - McKnight, F. H., 1919 (Folder 253: 7)
  - Marseille, 1919 (Folder 253: 8)
  - Merriles, A. H., 1919 (Folder 253: 9-10)
  - N correspondence, 1919 (Folder 253: 11)
  - Neal, Charles T., 1919 (Folder 253: 12)
  - Newcastle-on-Tyne, 1919 (Folder 253: 13)
  - Norway, 1918-1919 (Folder 253: 14)
  - O correspondence, 1919 (Folder 253: 15)
  - P correspondence, 1919 (Folder 253: 16)
  - Peden, E. A., 1919 (Folder 253: 17)
  - Plymouth, 1919 (Folder 253: 18)
  - Portugal, 1919 (Folder 253: 19)
  - Quinn, C. J. C., 1919 (Folder 253: 20)
  - R correspondence, 1919 (Folder 253: 21)
  - Randall, R. W., 1919 (Folder 254: 1)
  - Return cargoes, 1919 (Folder 254: 2)
  - Rotterdam, 1919 (Folder 254: 3-10)
  - Romania, 1918-1919 (Folder 254: 11)
  - S correspondence, 1919 (Folder 254: 12)
  - St. Nazaire, 1919 (Folder 254: 13)
  - Salonika, 1919 (Folder 254: 14)
  - Serbia, 1918-1919 (Folder 254: 15)
  - Sherman, Edwin, 1919 (Folder 254: 16)
  - Ships, 1919, 1947 (Folder 255)
    - "Daily Position of Ships reports, ", 1919, 1947 (Folder 255: 1-5)
    - Journal Sheet (List of ships in use), 1919 (Folder 255: 6)
    - "Steamer Movement reports, ", 1919 (Folder 255: 7-11)
  - Smith, H. B., 1919 (Folder 255: 12-15)
  - Smith, H. M., 1919 (Folder 256: 1)
  - Sprott, Elise I., 1919 (Folder 256: 2)
  - Stocks and sales, 1919 (Folder 256: 3-6)
  - Strauss, Lewis L., 1919 (Folder 256: 7)
  - Surface, Frank M., 1919 (Folder 256: 8)
  - Sweden, 1919 (Folder 256: 9)
  - Switzerland, 1918-1919 (Folder 256: 10)
  - T correspondence, 1918 (Folder 256: 11)
  - Taft, Robert, 1919 (Folder 256: 12)
  - Tours, 1919 (Folder 256: 13)
  - Trieste, 1919 (Folder 256: 14-16)
  - U.S. Army, 1919 (Folder 256: 17)
  - U.S. Navy, 1919 (Folder 256: 18-19)
  - U.S. Navy, 1919 (contd.) (Folder 257: 1-2)
  - U.S. Shipping Board, 1919 (Folder 257: 3-5)
  - W correspondence, 1919 (Folder 257: 6)
  - Wheat Executive, Royal Commission on Wheat Supplies, 1918-1919 (Folder 257: 7-9)
- United States Grain Corporation (USGC) New York office records, 1914-1928, 1939 (Folder 257-270)
  - Correspondence, 1917-1920
    - Herbert Hoover and Julius Barnes, U.S. Wheat Director, 1917-1918 (Folder 257: 10-16)
    - Herbert Hoover and Julius Barnes, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 258: 1-15)
    - Herbert Hoover and Julius Barnes, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 259: 1-18)
    - Herbert Hoover and Julius Barnes, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 260: 1-5)
    - Julius Barnes and Prentiss Gray, Marin Transportation Division, 1918-1919 (Folder 260: 6-17)
    - Julius Barnes and Prentiss Gray, 1918-1919 (contd.) (Folder 261: 1-11)
    - Julius Barnes and Howard M. Smith, Assistant Secretary, 1919-1920 (Folder 261: 12-15)
  - War Fact Tests for Graduation & Promotion, by William H. Allen, 1918 (Folder 262: 1)
  - Grain Exchanges; Hearing before The Committee on Rules, 1914 (Folder 262: 2)
  - Minutes of meetings of the Board of Directors, 1917-1919 (Folder 262: 3-5)
  - Montforte, Norman, 1920-1921 (Folder 262: 6-8)
  - Moore, Watson, 1917-1918 (Folder 262: 9)
  - Neal, Charles T., 1918 (Folder 262: 10)
  - Nye, A., 1918-1920 (Folder 262: 11)
  - Smith, H. M., 1918-1919 (Folder 262: 12-16)
  - Grain Corporation Book I, II, 1917-1919 (Folder 263: 1-6)
  - Flesh, Edward M., 1917-1919 (Folder 263: 7-15)
  - Julius H. Barnes, 1917-1918 (Folder 263: 16-18)
  - Julius H. Barnes, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 264: 1-2)
  - Weekly reports to Herbert Hoover, 1917-1919 (Folder 264: 3-6)
  - Daily reports "Wheat on Hand," 10/16/17 - 8/2/18 (Folder 264: 7-10)
  - Shattuck, Edwin P., 1919-1921, 1939 (Folder 264: 11-13)
  - Flesh, Edward M., 1920-1926 (Folder 264: 14-16)
  - Staley, F. S., 1919-1921 (Folder 265: 1-2)
  - Stream, J. J., 1917-1918 (Folder 265: 3-8)
  - New organization, 1919-1921 (Folder 265: 9)
  - Accounting procedures, 1917-1918, 1928 (Folder 265: 10)
  - All departments, 1918-1920 (Folder 265: 11)
  - Anglo-American Commercial Corporation, 1919-1920 (Folder 265: 12)
  - Appointments, 1917 (Folder 265: 13)
  - Babcock, Julia, 1920 (Folder 265: 14)
  - Bean department, 1918-1919 (Folder 265: 15)
  - Belgian department, 1918-1919 (Folder 265: 16)
  - Belgian government, 1920 (Folder 265: 17)
  - Book of information, 1919 (Folder 265: 18)
  - Brandeis, Alfred, 1919 (Folder 265: 19)
  - Bulletins, 1918-1920 (Folder 265: 20)
  - Cereal Division, 1918 (Folder 265: 21)
  - Certificate of membership, 1918 (Folder 265: 22)
  - Coarse grains, 1919 (Folder 265: 23)
  - Commission for Relief in Belgium, 1918 (Folder 265: 24)
  - Conferences, 1918 (Folder 266: 1-2)
  - Contract with ARA, 1919 (Folder 266: 3)
  - Corn, specification and prices, 1918-1919 (Folder 266: 4)
  - Crowell, F. G., 1917-1919 (Folder 266: 5-6)
  - Dudley, John, 1920-1926 (Folder 266: 7-8)
  - Eaton, William, 1919-1920 (Folder 266: 9)
  - European Department, 1919-1920 (Folder 266: 10)
  - Edgar, William C., 1918 (Folder 266: 11)
  - Flour, 1918-1920 (Folder 266)
    - Clippings, 1920 (Folder 266: 12)
    - Weekly reports, 1918-1920 (Folder 266: 13)
    - Distribution, 1920 (Folder 266: 14)
    - Department, 1918-1920 (Folder 266: 15)
    - Transit from Pacific to Atlantic Coast, 1919-1920 (Folder 266: 16)
  - Foster, W. H., 1918-1919 (Folder 266: 17-19)
  - France, 1919 (Folder 267: 1)
  - Frick, A. W., 1918-1919 (Folder 267: 2)
  - Gerks, 1918 (Folder 267: 3)
  - Grain zone agents, 1917 (Folder 267: 4)
  - Hall, G. Roy, 1918-1919 (Folder 267: 5)
  - Heguembourg, K.D., 1918 (Folder 267: 6)
  - Hitchcock, C. N., 1918-1920 (Folder 267: 7)
  - Memoranda for Herbert Hoover, 1917-1919 (Folder 267: 8)
  - Hyslop, George K., 1918-1920 (Folder 267: 9)
  - Insurance Advisory Committee, 1920 (Folder 267: 10)
  - Jackson, George, 1918 (Folder 267: 11)
  - Jackson, Howard, 1918 (Folder 267: 12)
  - Law Department, 1917 (Folder 267: 13)
  - Leslie, Banks & Company, 1918-1920 (Folder 267: 14-17)
  - Lingham, Fred, J., 1918-1919 (Folder 267: 18)
  - Lynahan, Margaret, 1918-1919 (Folder 267: 19)
  - Mechanics and Metals National Bank, 1918-1920 (Folder 267: 20-22)
  - Personnel, 1918-1921 (Folder 268: 1-2)
  - Piazzek, D. F., 1918 (Folder 268: 3)
  - Planes, Policies, and Activities, reports, 1918-1919 (Folder 268: 4-7)
  - Policies and Plan of Operation, October 19, 1917 (Folder 268: 8)
  - Press releases, 1919-1920 (Folder 268: 9)
  - Rice, 1919 (Folder 268: 10)
  - Russell, A. L., 1918-1919 (Folder 268: 11)
  - Salary Committee, 1917-1920 (Folder 268: 12)
  - Shipping Department, 1919 (Folder 268: 13)
  - The Story of the United States Grain Corporation, 1920 (Folder 268: 14)
  - Wheat export, 1918-1919 (Folder 268: 15-16)
  - Grain exchanges, 1918 (Folder 268: 17)
  - Grain data (tabulations), 1918 (Folder 269: 1-4)
  - New grain rules, 1918 (Folder 269: 5)
  - Statistics, 1917-1919 (Folder 269: 6-8)
  - Grosser, F. S., 1919 (Folder 269: 9)
  - McMillan, Fred, 1919 (Folder 269: 10)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, 1918-1919 (Folder 269: 11-12)
  - Official Statement of the United States Wheat Director, 1919-1920 (Folder 269: 13)
  - Interim Report of the Purchasing Commission for Russian Relief, March 25, 1922 (Folder 269: 14)
  - Grain and Flour Statistics during the War, by A. L. Russell, 1919 (Folder 269: 15)
  - Finances, 1918-1920 (Folder 270: 1-5)
  - Julius H. Barnes, 1919-1920 (Folder 270: 6-7)
  - Proclamations and Executive Orders by the President, 1917-1918 (Folder 270: 8-9)
- Edwin Paul Shattuck, General Counsel of the United States Grain Corporation (USGC), London office files, 1911-1934, 1957. (Folder 270-300)
  See also boxes 217-234, 375-376
  - Moore, Watson S., zone 7, 1919-1920 (Folder 270: 10)
  - Murray elevator explosion, 1919-1920 (Folder 270: 11)
  - Mystic (steamer) file, 1919 (Folder 270: 12-13)
  - Piazzek, D. F., zone 5, 1919-1920 (Folder 270: 14)
  - McCann, Alfred, 1920 (Folder 270: 15)
  - Palmer, A. Mitchell, 1919-1920 (Folder 270: 16)
  - Plans, Polices, and Activities, reports, 1920 (Folder 270: 17-18)
  - Plans, Polices, and Activities, reports, 1920 (contd.) (Folder 271: 1-2)
  - Port and Sales Committee, 1919 (Folder 271: 3)
  - Polish credit, 1919-1920 (Folder 271: 4)
  - Porto Rico government Food Commission, 1919 (Folder 271: 5)
  - USGC vs. Medicine Lodge Milling Company, 1919-1921 (Folder 271: 6-14)
  - To Mills in the New England Zone, bulletin, 1919 (Folder 271: 15)
  - USGC vs. Wallace B. Phillips, 1919-1923 (Folder 271: 16-17)
  - USGC vs. Wallace B. Phillips, 1919-1923 (contd.) (Folder 272: 1-11)
  - USGC vs. Wallace B. Phillips, 1919-1923 (contd.) (Folder 273: 1-9)
  - National Archives photocopies from 1917-1925 documents, 1957 (Folder 273: 10)
  - Daily press reports, 1919-1920 (Folder 273: 11-14)
  - Rates, 1919 (Folder 273: 15)
  - Railroad claims, 1919-1921 (Folder 273: 16-17)
  - Prisoners of war, 1918-1920 (Folder 274: 1-7)
  - Shawmut Steamship Company, 1919-1920 (Folder 274: 8)
  - Starr W. A., zone 12, 1919 (Folder 274: 9)
  - Proclamations, 1918 (Folder 274: 10-11)
  - Chicago billings, 1918-1922 (Folder 274: 12-14)
  - Sparks Milling Co., 1919-1927 (Folder 274: 15-16)
  - Hodgson Oil Refining Co., 1922-1927 (Folder 275: 1)
  - Rogers Grain Co., 1921-1927 (Folder 275: 2-3)
  - Sigurd Bruusgard, owner of the Norwegian Bark Clyde, 1924-1927 (Folder 275: 4-5)
  - Jefferson Insurance Co., 1925-1929 (Folder 275: 6)
  - John V. Quackenbush & Son Co., 1919-1928 (Folder 275: 7-9)
  - Richey, Lawrence, Investigating Department, weekly reports, 1919-1920 (Folder 275: 10-11)
  - Rickard, Edgar, 1919-1920 (Folder 275: 12)
  - Romanian accounts, 1919 (Folder 275: 13)
  - Russian credit, 1919-1920 (Folder 275: 14)
  - Russian relief, 1921-1922 (Folder 275: 15)
  - Mr. Ryan, 1919 (Folder 275: 16)
  - Seaver, F. S., 1919-1920 (Folder 275: 17)
  - Serbian accounts, 1920 (Folder 275: 18)
  - 2nd vice presidents, memoranda and instructions, 1919-1920 (Folder 275: 19-20)
  - Shipping Bill, 1920 (Folder 276: 1)
  - Shipping Board, 1920-1922 (Folder 276: 2-4)
  - Van Sooy, A. T., 1920 (Folder 276: 5)
  - Van Dusen, F. C., 1919 (Folder 276: 6)
  - Twist Brothers, 1919-1920 (Folder 276: 7)
  - Treasury Department, 1920-1923 (Folder 276: 8)
  - Tax on freight, 1919 (Folder 276: 9)
  - Stock purchase, 1919 (Folder 276: 10)
  - Tincher, representative of Medicine Lodge Milling Co., 1920 (Folder 276: 11)
  - State taxation, 1919-1921 (Folder 276: 12)
  - Staley, Frank, 1919-1920 (Folder 276: 13)
  - Sugar insurance, 1918 (Folder 276: 14-15)
  - Russian sugar, 1917-1918, 1926 (Folder 276: 16-17)
  - Foreign laws, 1919 (Folder 276: 18)
  - Memoranda of law, 1919 (Folder 276: 19)
  - Cuban Export Committee, 1919 (Folder 276: 20)
  - Injunction proceedings, 1918-1919 (Folder 277: 1-2)
  - Lewis E. Sands Co. Inc., 1919 (Folder 277: 3-8)
  - Seaboard exports, 1917 (Folder 277: 9-10)
  - Food Administration license revocation form, 1917 (Folder 277: 11)
  - Wheat Director license revocation form, 1919 (Folder 277: 12)
  - French government, food supplies to Russian prisoners in Germany, 1919-1921 (Folder 278: 1)
  - Winding up the Affairs of the USFA, USGC and U.S. Wheat Director, 1920 (Folder 278: 2-4)
  - Enforcement work under U.S. Wheat Director and Food Administration, reports, 1919-1920 (Folder 278: 5-6)
  - Tax matters, 1915-1921 (Folder 278: 7-9)
  - Agreements, 1919 (Folder 278: 10)
  - Trade licenses, 1918-1919 (Folder 278: 11-12)
  - Berkley Springs Milling Co., 1919 (Folder 278: 13)
  - Canio Caposello, 1919 (Folder 278: 14)
  - Herman Kraut, 1918 (Folder 278: 15)
  - Kensington Mills, 1919 (Folder 278: 16)
  - Trinidad National Bank, 1919 (Folder 278: 17)
  - Wheat Export Co., vs. The New Century Co., 1919 (Folder 279: 1)
  - Keystone Warehouse Co., 1919-1923 (Folder 279: 2)
  - Calumet Transportation Co., 1920 (Folder 279: 3)
  - Trial balances, 1919-1921 (Folder 279: 4-12)
  - ARA, 1919 (Folder 280: 1-2)
  - Crop of 1919 (Folder 280: 3)
  - Opinions on licenses, 1919 (Folder 280: 4)
  - Pacific Coast refineries, 1918-1919 (Folder 280: 5)
  - Rules and regulations, 1917-1918 (Folder 280: 6-8)
  - Watson, H. H., 1919 (Folder 280: 9-10)
  - Wheat Export Co., 1918-1920 (Folder 280: 11)
  - Wheat Director, 1920 (Folder 280: 12)
  - Whitmash, Theodor, 1918-1919 (Folder 280: 13)
  - Union Salvage and Cleaning Co., 1919-1920 (Folder 280: 14)
  - U.S. Sugar Equalization Board, 1916-1928
  - Printed matter, 1917-1926 (Folder 280: 15-16)
  - Printed matter, 1917-1926 (contd.) (Folder 281: 1-5)
  - P. DeRonde & Co., Inc., 1921-1926. (Folder 281: 6-9)
    See also box 282 and 283
  - Carlos Alfert & Co., 1922 (Folder 281: 10)
  - Binghamton Candy Co., 1922 (Folder 281: 11)
  - International Sugar Committee (Caribbean Committee), 1921-1922 (Folder 281: 12)
  - Compañia Industrial y Havierra Cubana, 1921-1922 (Folder 282: 1)
  - Waters, J. H., 1922 (Folder 282: 2)
  - Varounis, George S., 1921 (Folder 282: 3)
  - G. H. Finlay & Co., 1922-1923 (Folder 282: 4)
  - B. H. Howell, Son & Co., 1921-1925 (Folder 282: 5-6)
  - Carrett & Co., 1925-1927 (Folder 282: 7-8)
  - Argentine sugar, 1921-1928 (Folder 282: 9-11)
  - Finnish government files, regarding requisition of sugar and flour, 1917-1923 (Folder 282: 12-16)
  - Mobilization of the Sugar Industry, circa 1918 (Folder 283: 1)
  - P. DeRonde & Company, Inc., 1923-1927
  - Pleadings, 1923-1925 (Folder 283: 2-3)
  - Supreme Court of the U.S., petitioner's brief, 1925-1926 (Folder 283: 4)
  - General papers, 1923-1927 (Folder 283: 5-7)
  - Memoranda, 1923-1925 (Folder 283: 8-10)
  - Brief in Circuit Court of Appeals, 1924-1925 (Folder 283: 11)
  - Brief in Circuit Court of Appeals, 1924-1925 (contd.) (Folder 284: 1-2)
  - Correspondence, 1923-1927 (Folder 284: 3-6)
  - Printed matters, 1924-1926 (Folder 284: 7-10)
  - Printed matters, 1924-1926 (contd.) (Folder 285: 1-3)
  - Demurrage claims, 1919-1923 (Folder 285: 4-16)
  - Federal Sugar Refining Co., 1917-1926 (Folder 286)
  - Norwegian case, 1917-1918 (Folder 286: 1-7)
  - International Sugar Committee, minutes, 1917-1918 (Folder 286: 8-11)
  - General papers, 1919-1922 (Folder 286: 12-17)
  - General papers, 1919-1922 (contd.) (Folder 287: 1)
  - Printed matters, 1917-1921 (Folder 287: 2-6)
  - Agreements, 1919-1925 (Folder 287: 7-11)
  - Board records, 1918-1921 (Folder 287: 12)
  - Norwegian and Danish depositions, 1918-1922 (Folder 287: 13-15)
  - Defendant's Reply Brief, 1920 (Folder 288: 1)
  - Agreements, 1919 (Folder 288: 2-3)
  - Action on account, 1918-1922 (Folder 288: 4-11)
  - Insurance claims, 1919-1926 (Folder 288: 12-16)
  - Shipping Board, insurance rates on wooden vessels, 1918-1923 (Folder 289: 1-4)
  - Norwegian ship Songvig, 1916-1918 (Folder 289: 5-7)
  - Herbert Hoover files, 1917-1924 (Folder 289)
  - Personnel, 1919-1920 (Folder 289: 8)
  - Reports on Cases of Enforcement, 1918 (Folder 289: 9)
  - Orris W. Roberts, 1924 (Folder 289: 10)
  - John W. Swift, 1923 (Folder 289: 11)
  - Wheat, 1918 (Folder 289: 12)
  - Memoranda for Second Vice-Presidents and Managers of Agencies, 1917 (Folder 289: 13)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture records, 1917-1927 (Folder 289)
  - General, 1918-1920 (Folder 289: 14)
  - H. C. Stuart, 1919-1919 (Folder 289: 15)
  - David F. Houston, 1917-1918 (Folder 289: 16-19)
  - David F. Houston, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 290: 1-2)
  - Correspondence, reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 290: 3-9)
  - Carl L. Alsberg, 1917-1918 (Folder 290: 10-12)
  - Floyd R. Harrison, 1917-1918 (Folder 290: 13-14)
  - Agriculture Advisory Committee, 1917-1918 (Folder 290)
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 290: 14)
    - Speeches, 1918 (Folder 290: 16)
    - Meetings, 1918 (Folder 290: 17-19)
    - Meetings, 1918 (contd.) (Folder 291: 1-4)
    - Sub-committees, 1918 (Folder 291: 5)
  - Allied Provisions Export Commission, 1917-1918 (Folder 291: 6-7)
  - B correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 291: 8)
  - Babst, Earl D., 1917-1918 (Folder 291: 9)
  - Beer, 1917 (Folder 291: 10)
  - British War Mission, 1917-1918 (Folder 291: 11)
  - British Embassy, 1917-1918 (Folder 291: 12-14)
  - C correspondence, 1918 (Folder 291: 15)
  - Department of Commerce, 1917-1918 (Folder 292: 1-2)
  - Conservation in the manufacture of alcoholic beverages, 1917-1918 (Folder 292: 3)
  - Cotton, Josef P., 1917-1918 (Folder 292: 4-16)
  - Council of National Defense, 1917-1918 (Folder 292: 17)
  - D correspondence, 1918 (Folder 293: 1)
  - Dairy, 1918 (Folder 293: 2)
  - Denmark, 1917 (Folder 293: 3)
  - Federal Reserve Board, 1917-1918 (Folder 293: 4)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1917-1918 (Folder 293: 5-7)
  - France, 1917 (Folder 293: 8)
  - France, American Embassy, 1917-1918 (Folder 293: 9-11)
  - French Ambassador J. J. Jusserand, 1917 (Folder 293: 12)
  - French High Commission, 1917-1918 (Folder 293: 13)
  - French High Commissioner André Tardieu, 1917-1918 (Folder 293: 14)
  - French Minister of Food Victor Boret, 1918 (Folder 293: 15)
  - G correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 293: 16)
  - Glasgow, William A., 1918 (Folder 293: 17)
  - Grain dealers, 1917-1918 (Folder 294: 1)
  - H correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 294: 2)
  - Holland, 1917-1918 (Folder 294: 3)
  - House of Representatives, 1917-1918 (Folder 294: 4-8)
  - I correspondence, 1918 (Folder 294: 9)
  - Italian Embassy, 1918 (Folder 294: 10-11)
  - J correspondence, 1918 (Folder 294: 12)
  - Justice, Department of, 1917-1918 (Folder 294: 13)
  - K correspondence, 1918 (Folder 294: 14)
  - L correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 294: 15)
  - Lamborn & Co., 1917-1918 (Folder 294: 16)
  - Lever, Asbury F., 1917-1918 (Folder 294: 17-19)
  - Livestock Association, 1971 (Folder 295: 1)
  - London, American Embassy, 1918 (Folder 295: 2)
  - London Ministry of Food, 1917-1919 (Folder 295: 3-9)
  - M correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 295: 10)
  - McAdoo, William G., 1918 (Folder 295: 11)
  - Meat for the U.S. Army, 1918 (Folder 295: 12)
  - Meat Packers' Sub-Committee, 1918 (Folder 295: 13)
    1922
  - Meat Polices Sub-Committee, 1917-1918 (Folder 295: 14)
  - Meeker, Arthur, 1917-1918 (Folder 295: 15)
  - Navy Department, 1917-1918 (Folder 295)
    - Alphabetical file, 1917-1918 (Folder 295: 16-17)
    - Josephus Daniels, Secretary of the Navy, correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 295: 18)
    - Bureau of Supplies and Accounts, 1917 (Folder 295: 19)